export const Questions = [
  {
    id: "cf7fce29-564c-4aaa-97de-7981c3c6e26f",
    question:
      "A company offers a software product with a 25% discount. If the discounted price is \u20b975,000, what was the original price?",
    options: ["\u20b990,000", "\u20b9100,000", "\u20b980,000", "\u20b995,000"],
    correctOption: "\u20b9100,000",
  },
  {
    id: "f4922a5d-8407-4134-81b5-a7d852c5d971",
    question:
      "A BDE targets to increase sales by 15% this quarter. If the last quarter's sales were \u20b98,00,000, what is the new target?",
    options: [
      "\u20b99,20,000",
      "\u20b99,30,000",
      "\u20b99,00,000",
      "\u20b98,60,000",
    ],
    correctOption: "\u20b99,20,000",
  },
  {
    id: "aa317662-533c-46a4-9065-e98d31bc1659",
    question:
      "If a client negotiates a 12% reduction on a \u20b950,000 quotation, what is the final price?",
    options: ["\u20b946,000", "\u20b944,000", "\u20b943,500", "\u20b945,000"],
    correctOption: "\u20b944,000",
  },
  {
    id: "175b1ec4-0240-4841-875c-6d3e669fe8ec",
    question:
      "A BDE needs to arrange a demo in 3 days but resources are available only after 5 days. What's the best action?",
    options: [
      "Delay the demo without informing",
      "Arrange alternative resources",
      "Ignore the client's request",
      "Cancel the demo",
    ],
    correctOption: "Arrange alternative resources",
  },
  {
    id: "e3c44a66-bf43-440f-aa39-bd7b30c0995f",
    question: "Which metric best measures a BDE\u2019s success?",
    options: [
      "Number of cold calls made",
      "Revenue generated",
      "Emails sent",
      "Hours worked",
    ],
    correctOption: "Revenue generated",
  },
  {
    id: "2410ddf9-74b9-407d-af8c-85e27233f1c1",
    question: "Which of the following is a CRM tool?",
    options: ["Jira", "Salesforce", "Slack", "Figma"],
    correctOption: "Salesforce",
  },
  {
    id: "49bddbf4-1dec-4387-8757-75cdebd82072",
    question:
      "During a client meeting, what is the best way to handle objections?",
    options: [
      "Ignore and proceed",
      "Listen carefully and provide solutions",
      "Argue back",
      "End the meeting immediately",
    ],
    correctOption: "Listen carefully and provide solutions",
  },
  {
    id: "e155540f-fda4-43e0-84db-b12e4c9ceb33",
    question: "What does BANT stand for in lead qualification?",
    options: [
      "Baseline, Action, Need, Terms",
      "Business, Agreement, Negotiation, Team",
      "Benefit, Analysis, Network, Time",
      "Budget, Authority, Need, Timeline",
    ],
    correctOption: "Budget, Authority, Need, Timeline",
  },
  {
    id: "c374b3aa-77c9-4204-ac2c-e089fb67fdcd",
    question:
      "A client asks for a feature not available in the product. What should a BDE do?",
    options: [
      "Say yes without checking",
      "Politely inform and suggest alternatives",
      "Ignore the request",
      "Promise and later inform it's unavailable",
    ],
    correctOption: "Politely inform and suggest alternatives",
  },
  {
    id: "74f361ce-d091-44c9-9945-a75aff74635e",
    question: "Which one is important for cold calling?",
    options: [
      "Understanding client needs",
      "Avoiding client questions",
      "Speaking fast",
      "Talking about yourself",
    ],
    correctOption: "Understanding client needs",
  },
  {
    id: "5c3673d6-9755-4703-962e-d8df8396ccaf",
    question: "What does BDE stand for?",
    options: [
      "Business Data Expert",
      "Brand Design Engineer",
      "Business Development Executive",
      "Backend Developer Expert",
    ],
    correctOption: "Business Development Executive",
  },
  {
    id: "e7fe6d40-cee8-41b6-8cc3-2668b7eb4fc4",
    question: "What is the main role of a BDE?",
    options: [
      "Manage internal IT support",
      "Handle accounts",
      "Develop websites",
      "Increase business opportunities",
    ],
    correctOption: "Increase business opportunities",
  },
  {
    id: "f6777cdb-46e4-45d9-8f9b-6d921317ac65",
    question: "Cold calling is associated with which phase?",
    options: [
      "Product Development",
      "Customer Support",
      "Billing",
      "Lead Generation",
    ],
    correctOption: "Lead Generation",
  },
  {
    id: "713291a8-1c49-4e38-9718-63cd8596677f",
    question: "In email communication, which one is most important?",
    options: [
      "Using slang words",
      "Clear subject line",
      "Writing long emails",
      "Adding irrelevant attachments",
    ],
    correctOption: "Clear subject line",
  },
  {
    id: "77930b9e-4e6f-48a9-8dac-11dec7256f32",
    question: "Which skill is most important for a BDE?",
    options: [
      "Graphic Designing",
      "Technical writing",
      "Communication skills",
      "Coding",
    ],
    correctOption: "Communication skills",
  },
  {
    id: "acfae2c4-a052-4e9a-904a-9b0a37a4843d",
    question:
      "A company offers a software product with a 25% discount. If the discounted price is \u20b975,000, what was the original price?",
    options: ["\u20b990,000", "\u20b9100,000", "\u20b995,000", "\u20b980,000"],
    correctOption: "\u20b9100,000",
  },
  {
    id: "01897087-4456-4b7a-8e4b-ff30fd643f22",
    question:
      "A BDE targets to increase sales by 15% this quarter. If the last quarter's sales were \u20b98,00,000, what is the new target?",
    options: [
      "\u20b99,00,000",
      "\u20b98,60,000",
      "\u20b99,30,000",
      "\u20b99,20,000",
    ],
    correctOption: "\u20b99,20,000",
  },
  {
    id: "2f55d5ed-3505-443a-bed2-5f4be72ec2f4",
    question:
      "If a client negotiates a 12% reduction on a \u20b950,000 quotation, what is the final price?",
    options: ["\u20b944,000", "\u20b943,500", "\u20b945,000", "\u20b946,000"],
    correctOption: "\u20b944,000",
  },
  {
    id: "110aaa16-003e-48df-843b-e6ce93bb2919",
    question:
      "A BDE needs to arrange a demo in 3 days but resources are available only after 5 days. What's the best action?",
    options: [
      "Delay the demo without informing",
      "Ignore the client's request",
      "Cancel the demo",
      "Arrange alternative resources",
    ],
    correctOption: "Arrange alternative resources",
  },
  {
    id: "ed0e8459-9321-4f50-bdcd-8d88b639bbad",
    question: "Which metric best measures a BDE\u2019s success?",
    options: [
      "Number of cold calls made",
      "Emails sent",
      "Hours worked",
      "Revenue generated",
    ],
    correctOption: "Revenue generated",
  },
  {
    id: "6c9e5b65-99b1-41e9-9cbd-0f9d8e3752e0",
    question: "Which of the following is a CRM tool?",
    options: ["Jira", "Salesforce", "Slack", "Figma"],
    correctOption: "Salesforce",
  },
  {
    id: "d65cb321-332f-41d1-ab58-18e51053b41e",
    question:
      "During a client meeting, what is the best way to handle objections?",
    options: [
      "Argue back",
      "Listen carefully and provide solutions",
      "End the meeting immediately",
      "Ignore and proceed",
    ],
    correctOption: "Listen carefully and provide solutions",
  },
  {
    id: "b7ab2fbe-7cf4-46d8-a0d9-0ebe5265635b",
    question: "What does BANT stand for in lead qualification?",
    options: [
      "Business, Agreement, Negotiation, Team",
      "Baseline, Action, Need, Terms",
      "Budget, Authority, Need, Timeline",
      "Benefit, Analysis, Network, Time",
    ],
    correctOption: "Budget, Authority, Need, Timeline",
  },
  {
    id: "38ccef36-2e30-42b9-8c56-17efe3f471f8",
    question:
      "A client asks for a feature not available in the product. What should a BDE do?",
    options: [
      "Promise and later inform it's unavailable",
      "Say yes without checking",
      "Politely inform and suggest alternatives",
      "Ignore the request",
    ],
    correctOption: "Politely inform and suggest alternatives",
  },
  {
    id: "275193f0-d973-476e-ba3a-a3c1515d3952",
    question: "Which one is important for cold calling?",
    options: [
      "Talking about yourself",
      "Speaking fast",
      "Avoiding client questions",
      "Understanding client needs",
    ],
    correctOption: "Understanding client needs",
  },
  {
    id: "1f456ccf-bb45-4c30-9a8d-bc8e95b6cdbd",
    question: "What does BDE stand for?",
    options: [
      "Backend Developer Expert",
      "Business Data Expert",
      "Brand Design Engineer",
      "Business Development Executive",
    ],
    correctOption: "Business Development Executive",
  },
  {
    id: "14bb5354-5faf-45f8-a42c-bd6283e31e87",
    question: "What is the main role of a BDE?",
    options: [
      "Handle accounts",
      "Manage internal IT support",
      "Develop websites",
      "Increase business opportunities",
    ],
    correctOption: "Increase business opportunities",
  },
  {
    id: "91d2da75-3ee6-4fef-b37a-6e2ebc07604a",
    question: "Cold calling is associated with which phase?",
    options: [
      "Customer Support",
      "Lead Generation",
      "Product Development",
      "Billing",
    ],
    correctOption: "Lead Generation",
  },
  {
    id: "a0a1d245-29b9-4cbf-9beb-9bfa16f82e1d",
    question: "In email communication, which one is most important?",
    options: [
      "Clear subject line",
      "Writing long emails",
      "Adding irrelevant attachments",
      "Using slang words",
    ],
    correctOption: "Clear subject line",
  },
  {
    id: "c8a16821-5d99-4ad5-a288-f6cd80bf8d02",
    question: "Which skill is most important for a BDE?",
    options: [
      "Coding",
      "Graphic Designing",
      "Technical writing",
      "Communication skills",
    ],
    correctOption: "Communication skills",
  },
  {
    id: "61ad8b92-d9b7-4aad-b2b5-5d6d85378418",
    question:
      "A company offers a software product with a 25% discount. If the discounted price is \u20b975,000, what was the original price?",
    options: ["\u20b980,000", "\u20b9100,000", "\u20b990,000", "\u20b995,000"],
    correctOption: "\u20b9100,000",
  },
  {
    id: "2126c8a8-c925-45aa-93ae-0a947bb8e983",
    question:
      "A BDE targets to increase sales by 15% this quarter. If the last quarter's sales were \u20b98,00,000, what is the new target?",
    options: [
      "\u20b99,20,000",
      "\u20b98,60,000",
      "\u20b99,00,000",
      "\u20b99,30,000",
    ],
    correctOption: "\u20b99,20,000",
  },
  {
    id: "bf860748-8385-4f91-8b8e-e6ab4589dc5a",
    question:
      "If a client negotiates a 12% reduction on a \u20b950,000 quotation, what is the final price?",
    options: ["\u20b944,000", "\u20b946,000", "\u20b945,000", "\u20b943,500"],
    correctOption: "\u20b944,000",
  },
  {
    id: "054cf119-1cd6-4662-a20b-dc6f507acfff",
    question:
      "A BDE needs to arrange a demo in 3 days but resources are available only after 5 days. What's the best action?",
    options: [
      "Cancel the demo",
      "Arrange alternative resources",
      "Ignore the client's request",
      "Delay the demo without informing",
    ],
    correctOption: "Arrange alternative resources",
  },
  {
    id: "5c694a1a-6e1e-4952-8a82-60183b9f5cc8",
    question: "Which metric best measures a BDE\u2019s success?",
    options: [
      "Emails sent",
      "Revenue generated",
      "Hours worked",
      "Number of cold calls made",
    ],
    correctOption: "Revenue generated",
  },
  {
    id: "102cfbe2-c32e-45fe-b218-092c9d373e73",
    question: "Which of the following is a CRM tool?",
    options: ["Figma", "Jira", "Slack", "Salesforce"],
    correctOption: "Salesforce",
  },
  {
    id: "69827ae3-df0d-42a3-82aa-d501c20a61dc",
    question:
      "During a client meeting, what is the best way to handle objections?",
    options: [
      "Ignore and proceed",
      "Argue back",
      "Listen carefully and provide solutions",
      "End the meeting immediately",
    ],
    correctOption: "Listen carefully and provide solutions",
  },
  {
    id: "62f0d2c0-ee34-4e25-8f5c-17a7ea9e4738",
    question: "What does BANT stand for in lead qualification?",
    options: [
      "Budget, Authority, Need, Timeline",
      "Baseline, Action, Need, Terms",
      "Business, Agreement, Negotiation, Team",
      "Benefit, Analysis, Network, Time",
    ],
    correctOption: "Budget, Authority, Need, Timeline",
  },
  {
    id: "191f13fa-a542-4588-b424-3325c69cd055",
    question:
      "A client asks for a feature not available in the product. What should a BDE do?",
    options: [
      "Ignore the request",
      "Say yes without checking",
      "Promise and later inform it's unavailable",
      "Politely inform and suggest alternatives",
    ],
    correctOption: "Politely inform and suggest alternatives",
  },
  {
    id: "2167f3fd-5069-4e7b-830d-127ad7532d51",
    question: "Which one is important for cold calling?",
    options: [
      "Speaking fast",
      "Understanding client needs",
      "Avoiding client questions",
      "Talking about yourself",
    ],
    correctOption: "Understanding client needs",
  },
  {
    id: "28325d5b-7a93-46a3-b3de-5fc64b9f4eb6",
    question: "What does BDE stand for?",
    options: [
      "Backend Developer Expert",
      "Business Data Expert",
      "Brand Design Engineer",
      "Business Development Executive",
    ],
    correctOption: "Business Development Executive",
  },
  {
    id: "f1fc7965-c51b-435d-aa47-743bad72bff2",
    question: "What is the main role of a BDE?",
    options: [
      "Handle accounts",
      "Develop websites",
      "Manage internal IT support",
      "Increase business opportunities",
    ],
    correctOption: "Increase business opportunities",
  },
  {
    id: "20fd4a62-c526-4394-85e4-ad1be9e47314",
    question: "Cold calling is associated with which phase?",
    options: [
      "Billing",
      "Customer Support",
      "Lead Generation",
      "Product Development",
    ],
    correctOption: "Lead Generation",
  },
  {
    id: "ba12317f-15bb-4fc2-952e-a363e0062935",
    question: "In email communication, which one is most important?",
    options: [
      "Clear subject line",
      "Using slang words",
      "Adding irrelevant attachments",
      "Writing long emails",
    ],
    correctOption: "Clear subject line",
  },
  {
    id: "66eb86ce-6a42-4c0e-b9dd-d24d717a9df5",
    question: "Which skill is most important for a BDE?",
    options: [
      "Communication skills",
      "Graphic Designing",
      "Technical writing",
      "Coding",
    ],
    correctOption: "Communication skills",
  },
  {
    id: "486ae85e-6750-4efb-b940-78b9cd327074",
    question:
      "A company offers a software product with a 25% discount. If the discounted price is \u20b975,000, what was the original price?",
    options: ["\u20b9100,000", "\u20b990,000", "\u20b995,000", "\u20b980,000"],
    correctOption: "\u20b9100,000",
  },
  {
    id: "3ac945ab-f0aa-423e-8fd5-d00b1a5399d5",
    question:
      "A BDE targets to increase sales by 15% this quarter. If the last quarter's sales were \u20b98,00,000, what is the new target?",
    options: [
      "\u20b99,30,000",
      "\u20b99,20,000",
      "\u20b98,60,000",
      "\u20b99,00,000",
    ],
    correctOption: "\u20b99,20,000",
  },
  {
    id: "e762e3ba-323a-4013-8b5a-296d14ca8d5a",
    question:
      "If a client negotiates a 12% reduction on a \u20b950,000 quotation, what is the final price?",
    options: ["\u20b946,000", "\u20b943,500", "\u20b944,000", "\u20b945,000"],
    correctOption: "\u20b944,000",
  },
  {
    id: "f8a394c0-edb9-4553-a086-76f0fd7f7547",
    question:
      "A BDE needs to arrange a demo in 3 days but resources are available only after 5 days. What's the best action?",
    options: [
      "Ignore the client's request",
      "Arrange alternative resources",
      "Cancel the demo",
      "Delay the demo without informing",
    ],
    correctOption: "Arrange alternative resources",
  },
  {
    id: "90f75e41-3016-4737-ba7d-8f5771c313a6",
    question: "Which metric best measures a BDE\u2019s success?",
    options: [
      "Revenue generated",
      "Number of cold calls made",
      "Hours worked",
      "Emails sent",
    ],
    correctOption: "Revenue generated",
  },
];
